<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Songs>
        <Song>
        <name>As it was</name>
        <genre>Pop rock/Funk/Synth pop</genre>
        <artist>Harry Styles</artist>
        <album>Harry's House</album>
        <year>2022</year>
        <lyrics>
            Holdin' me back
            Gravity's holdin' me back
            I want you to hold out the palm of your hand
            Why don't we leave it at that?
            Nothin' to say
            When everything gets in the way
            Seems you cannot be replaced
            And I'm the one who will stay, oh
            In this world, it's just us
            You know it's not the same as it was
            In this world, it's just us
            You know it's not the same as it was
            As it was, as it was
            You know it's not the same
            Answer the phone
            "Harry, you're no good alone
            Why are you sittin' at home on the floor?
            What kind of pills are you on?"
            Ringin' the bell
            And nobody's comin' to help
            Your daddy lives by himself
            He just wants to know that you're well, oh
            In this world, it's just us
            You know it's not the same as it was
            In this world, it's just us
            You know it's not the same as it was
            As it was, as it was
            You know it's not the same
            Go home, get ahead, light-speed internet
            I don't wanna talk about the way that it was
            Leave America, two kids follow her
            I don't wanna talk about who's doin' it first
            As it was
            You know it's not the same as it was
            As it was, as it was
        </lyrics>
        <MP3File>Canciones/As it was.wav</MP3File>
        </Song>

        <Song>
            <name>Latch</name>
            <genre>Deep house/Dance/Electronica</genre>
            <artist>Disclosure</artist>
            <album>Settle</album>
            <year>2013</year>
            <lyrics>
                You lift my heart up
                When the rest of me is down
                You, you enchant me, even when you're not around
                If there are boundaries, I will try to knock them down
                I'm latching on babe
                Now I know what I have found
                I feel we're close enough
                I wanna lock in your love
                I think we're close enough
                Could I lock in your love, baby?
                Now I got you in my space
                I won't let go of you
                Got you shackled in my embrace
                I'm latching on to you
                Now I got you in my space
                I won't let go of you
                Got you shackled in my embrace
                I'm latching on to you
                I'm so encaptured, got me wrapped up in your touch
                Feel so enamored, hold me tight within your clutch
                How do you do it, you got me losing every breath
                What did you give me to make my heart beat out my chest?
                I feel we're close enough
                I wanna lock in your love
                I think we're close enough
                Could I lock in your love, baby?
                I feel we're close enough
                I wanna lock in your love
                I think we're close enough
                Could I lock in your love, baby?
                Now I got you in my space
                I won't let go of you
                Got you shackled in my embrace
                I'm latching on to you
                Now I got you in my space
                I won't let go of you
                Got you shackled in my embrace
                I'm latching on to you
                I'm latching on to you (I'm latching on to you)
                I won't let go of you (I won't let go)
                I'm latching on to you (I don't wanna let go)
                I won't let go of you (I won't let go, I won't let go)
            </lyrics>
            <MP3File>Canciones/Latch.wav</MP3File>
        </Song>

        <Song>
            <name>MIRÁ MAMÁ</name>
            <genre>Urbano latino</genre>
            <artist>WOS</artist>
            <album>Oscuro éxtasis</album>
            <year>2021</year>
            <lyrics>
                Yo me vi largar las palabras, como un aguacero
                Pensamientos vienen muchos, solo algunos son sincero'
                ¿Qué voy a hacer si nunca me basé en los cero'?
                Tengo un nudo en la garganta y en la panza un agujero
                Sé que todo esto es pasajero
                La agonía del enfermo, el amor en el verano
                Su calor en el invierno
                Pero la veo y caigo en la trampa de sentir que hay algo eterno
                "¿Cómo estás?" Le contesto que no sé llorar
                Por eso dibujo lágrimas
                Ya se humedeció toda la página, así que imaginá
                Al menos no soy una máquina
                ¿Será que no quiero que esto muera y que se olviden de mí?
                Si te soy sincero
                ¿Será que no quiero darme cuenta que los que les creí
                No eran tan sincero'?
                Mirá mamá, estoy arriba
                Y te juro que no hay nada más que la vida
                Mirame acá, estoy arriba
                Y te juro que no hay nada más que la vida
                Mirá mamá, 'toy arriba
                Y te juro que no hay nada más que la vida
                Mirá mamá, estoy arriba
                Y te juro que no hay nada más
                Todo se deshace y quiero irme
                Cuando no puedo pisar firme en el mismo lugar que antes
                Pero todo son instante' y escapar no sirve
                Para buscar ser libre nunca se hace tarde
                Y ahora entendí
                Que no todo está bien pero está bien así
                Una temporada de poner énfasis
                En entender el lado oscuro de este éxtasis
                Y no es que sea frágil
                Es que tengo la nostalgia con el "Sí" muy fácil
                Sé que es difícil 'tar al lado mío
                Les da náuseas el vaivén de lo que vivo
                Te preguntabas por qué estando mojado me río
                Es que me empapa este rocío compuesto por recuerdos de crío
                En un banco rimando con frío
                Amando a los mío', tomando y tentando al olvido
                Y ahora dudo si eso tuyo era amor de verdad
                O buscabas un muñeco pa' mostrar
                Y no funcionó conmigo
                No soy un placebo diseñado pa' engañar tu vacío
                ¿Será que no quiero que esto muera y que se olviden de mí?
                Si te soy sincero
                ¿Será que no quiero darme cuenta que los que les creí
                No eran tan sincero'?
                Mirá mamá, estoy arriba
                Y te juro que no hay nada más que la vida
                Mirame acá, estoy arriba
                Y te juro que no hay nada más que la vida
                Mirá mamá, 'toy arriba
                Y te juro que no hay nada más que la vida
                Mirá mamá, estoy arriba
                Y te juro que no hay nada más, eh
                Mirá mamá, 'toy arriba
                Y te juro que no hay nada más que la vida
                Mira mamá, estoy arriba
                Y te juro que no hay nada más
            </lyrics>
            <MP3File>Canciones/MIRÁ MAMÁ.wav</MP3File>
        </Song>

        <Song>
            <name>Psycho (feat. Ty Dolla $ign)</name>
            <genre>Hip Hop/Electropop</genre>
            <artist>Post Malone/feat(Ty Dolla $ign)</artist>
            <album>Beerbongs and Bentleys</album>
            <year>2018</year>
            <lyrics>
                Damn, my AP goin' psycho, lil' mama bad like Michael
                Can't really trust nobody with all this jewelry on you
                My roof look like a no-show, got diamonds by the boatload
                Come with the Tony Romo for clowns and all the bozos
                My AP goin' psycho, lil' mama bad like Michael
                Can't really trust nobody with all this jewelry on you
                My roof look like a no-show, got diamonds by the boatload
                Don't act like you my friend when I'm rollin' through my ends, though

                You stuck in the friend zone, I tell that four-five the fifth
                Hunnid bands inside my shorts, DeChino the shit
                Try to stuff it all in, but it don't even fit
                Know that I been with the shits ever since a jit
                I made my first million, I'm like: Shit, this is it
                30 for a walkthrough, man, we had that bitch lit
                Had so many bottles, gave ugly girl a sip
                Out the window of the Benzo, we get seen in the rent'
                And I'm like: Whoa, man, my neck so goddamn cold
                Diamonds wet, my t-shirt soaked
                I got homies, let it go, oh
                My money thick, won't ever fold
                She said: Can I have some to hold?
                And I can't ever tell you no

                Damn, my AP goin' psycho, lil' mama bad like Michael
                Can't really trust nobody with all this jewelry on you
                My roof look like a no-show, got diamonds by the boatload
                Come with the Tony Romo for clowns and all the bozos
                My AP goin' psycho, lil' mama bad like Michael
                Can't really trust nobody with all this jewelry on you
                My roof look like a no-show, got diamonds by the boatload
                Don't act like you my friend when I'm rollin' through my ends, though

                [Ty Dolla $ign]
                The AP goin' psycho, my Rollie goin' brazy
                I'm hittin' lil' mama, she wanna have my babies
                It's fifty on the pinky, chain so stanky
                You should see the whip, promise I can take yo' bitch
                Dolla ridin' in an old school Chevy, it's a drop top
                Boolin' with a thot-thot, she gon' give me top-top
                Just one switch, I can make the ass drop
                Ayy, take you to the smoke shop
                We gon' get high, ayy, we gon' hit Rodeo
                Dial up Valentino, we gon' hit Pico
                Take you where I'm from, take you to the slums
                This ain't happen overnight, no, these diamonds real bright
                Saint Laurent jeans, still in my Vans though
                All VVS', put you in a necklace
                Girl, you look beautiful tonight
                Stars on the roof, they matching with the jewelry

                [Post Malone]
                Damn, my AP goin' psycho, lil' mama bad like Michael
                Can't really trust nobody with all this jewelry on you
                My roof look like a no-show, got diamonds by the boatload
                Come with the Tony Romo for clowns and all the bozos
                My AP goin' psycho, lil' mama bad like Michael
                Can't really trust nobody with all this jewelry on you
                My roof look like a no-show, got diamonds by the boatload
                Don't act like you my friend when I'm rollin' through my ends, though
            </lyrics>
            <MP3File>Canciones/Psycho (feat. Ty Dolla Sign).wav</MP3File>
        </Song>

        <Song>
            <name>Stuck With Me</name>
            <genre>Electropop/Dance pop</genre>
            <artist>The Neighbourhood</artist>
            <album>The Neighbourhood</album>
            <year>2018</year>
            <lyrics>
                Now I'm feeling guilty for it
                Didn't wanna leave
                I got caught up in the forest
                Hangin' with the trees
                Realised I'm less important
                Than I thought I'd be
                I'm not tellin' you for any certain reason but
                Now I'm feelin' guilty for it
                I didn't wanna leave, no
                I got caught up in the forest
                Hangin' with the trees, yeah, yeah
                Realized I'm less important (oh, yeah)
                Than I thought I'd be, yeah
                I'm not tellin' you for any certain reasons but
                I just want your empathy
                Our lives keep on gettin' shorter
                Losin' opportunity
                There might be some other ways of looking at it but
                That's just what I see
                I been gettin' over myself
                Thinkin' about what you need
                Then I realised that neither of us matter
                What's reality, yeah?
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with you
                Couldn't be more different than me
                So each time we agree
                I feel fulfilled
                You always end up stickin' to me
                Somehow, somehow
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with
                You are stuck with me
                So I guess I'll be sticking with
                You are stuck with me
            </lyrics>
            <MP3File>Canciones/Stuck with me.wav</MP3File>
        </Song>

        <Song>
            <name>The Spins</name>
            <genre>Hip-hop/Rap</genre>
            <artist>Mac Miller</artist>
            <album>K.I.D.S</album>
            <year>2010</year>
            <lyrics>
                Dope shit like that Jerm
                Oh hi
                Welcome back to K.I.D.S
                Umm, follow your dreams
                Yeah!
                Wanna get a mansion
                A jacuzzi, a theater to watch my movies
                A couple whips and lots of fancy things
                The kids they call the Goonies
                I see the future, crystal ball
                Mirror, mirror hangin' on the wall
                Who the flyest white boy of them dem all?
                Got your girlfriend screenin' all the calls
                She bubblin', we fuckin' then you cuddlin'
                Like baby where the fuck you been?
                Don't wanna tell you she in love with him
                So, so, we ain't sayin' nothing
                You could probably tell she bluffin'
                'Cause she kiss you with the mouth
                She gave me head with my concussion
                Yeah she blushin', all red
                Wanna rush and go to bed
                You interrogate that bitch like you the feds
                So she says
                She in love with a rock star, rock star
                Wanna smoke my weed
                So she asks me where the tops are, tops are
                Oh, oh, oh (top drawer, haha, yeah)
                Honey, I need you 'round (haha)
                I know, I know (just some motherfuckin' kids)
                Oh, oh, oh
                Honey, I need you 'round (make money, fuck bitches)
                I know, I know (yeah, Pittsburgh, hey, Jerm, hey)
                These hoes is drunk, wanna come and smoke this blunt
                Then let me take 'em home and do anything I want
                I said, "Baby, I can ride you, just let me get inside you
                I can take you higher if you hit this vaporizer"
                I got that dope dick, I'll be your supplier
                You grabbin' on my sheets and hittin' notes like you Mariah
                Obsessed with me
                Undress a freak on ecstasy
                I'm out and then she textin' me
                Like, "What you doin' next week, next week?" (yeah)
                Hear me now!
                I'm down on knees and praying
                Though my faith is weak
                Without you so please baby please
                Give us a chance
                Make amends and I will stand up 'til the end
                A million times, a trillion more
                Oh, oh, oh
                Honey, I need you 'round (I'm drunk as fuck)
                I know, I know (most Dope, bitch, hey)
                Oh, oh, oh (K.I.D.S., what's up?)
                Honey, I need you 'round (I'm high as fuck, yeah, yes, sir)
                I know, I know (oh, I graduated, oh yeah, I just graduated high school, haha)
                Hey, homie
                Don't be mad that your girl loves me (don't cut anything yet)
                It's not my fault (yeah)
                I'm just doin' me (haha)
                If your girl love me, let her love me, you feel me?
                So, baby smile (uh-huh)
                Baby, don't cry
                I will only fly
                With you by my side
            </lyrics>
            <MP3File>Canciones/The Spins.wav</MP3File>
        </Song>
</Songs>
